<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Writing Right</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="fragment_name_apa">\n\n\n APA Style</string>
    <string name="fragment_name_mla">\n\n\n MLA Style</string>
    <string name="fragment_name_chicago">\n\n\n Chicago Style</string>
    <string name="fragment_name_home">\n\n\n Home</string>
    <string name="fragment_name_harvard">\n\n\n Harvard Style</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>
    <string name="basics">
        <b><u><center>BASIC SET-UP IN MS WORD.</center>\n\n</u></b>
        <ul>
            <li> On the Page Layout menu select Margin then Normal.\n</li>
            <li> Font - Times New Roman.\n</li>
            <li>Font size -12.\n</li>
            <li>Line Spacing -Double 2.0.\n</li>
            <li>Margin -Normal {One inch on each side}.\n</li>
        </ul>
    </string>
    <string name="abstract_basic">
           <b><u><center> Abstract</center>\n\n</u></b>
        In this brief section the writer summarizes the major aspects that the entire paper
        covers in 100 to 300 words .it covers the purpose of the paper, major findings or
        claims made in the paper and the basic design of the paper and research methods. The
        main aim is to help the reader quickly ascertain the papers purpose.it may contain the
        purpose, results, scope and contents of the paper or the thesis, background and conclusion.

    </string>
    <string name="title">
    <b><u><center> Title</center>\n\n</u></b>
        To come up with a title try to clearly explain the purpose of your topic.
        Involve keywords and phrases that create a positive impression and avoid using abbreviations.

    </string>
    <string name="introduction">
    <b><u><center> Introduction </center>\n\n</u></b>
        The introduction should announce your topic and provide context and a rationale for your work .
        It should include statements about the subject to attract reader\’s attention and a background to
        the paper and explain why the research is important.
    </string>
    <string name="literature_review">
    <b><u><center> Literature Review </center>\n\n</u></b>
        This section includes a discussion or review of what is known
        about the subject or what other writers have written about your topic and how that knowledge was acquired.
    </string>
    <string name="main_body">
    <b><u><center> Main Body </center>\n\n</u></b>
        In this section the author supports the thesis and builds the argument. It contains most of the citations and analysis.
    </string>
    <string name="conclusion">
    <b><u><center> Conclusion </center>\n\n</u></b>
        This section brings together the points of the main paper and underscores what it all means without sounding redundant.
    </string>

    <string name="citations">
   <b><u><center> Citations</center>\n\n</u></b>
        <ul>
            <li>Refers to a reference to a published or unpublished source that was utilized to obtain information
                from and a chance to get information about earlier research.\n</li>
            <li>Citing sources is additionally best defence against plagiarism allegations.\n</li>
        </ul>



    </string>


    <string name="first_apa">

        <b><h1><center>APA</center></h1></b>

        <b><center>First Page\n\n</center></b>
            <b>Header\n</b>
             <ul>
            <li>Contains the Running Head preceded by the words RUNNING HEAD.\n</li>
            <li>Other pages shouldn\'t have the words RUNNING HEAD in the Running head.\n</li>
            <li>It should be aligned Right.\n</li>
	        <li>To enforce this use the Design Menu and check Different First page.\n</li>
            <li>Insert the Page Number at the top right of the header after Running Head. \n</li>
             </ul>
        <u><b><center>First Page</center></b>\n\n </u>
             <ul>
                <li>Write Title in the middle of the page usng Title Case\n</li>
                 <li> Write Name,then School followed by Date of Submission on a different line.\n</li>
             </ul>
        <u><b><center>Second Page.</center></b>\n</u>
            <ul>
                 <li> Insert header without the words “Running Head”.\n</li>
                 <li>Write title of your Essay in Title Case.\n</li>
                 <li> First paragraph is left aligned with the first sentence starting away from the margin,\n</li>

             </ul>
</string>
    <string name="last_apa">
       <u><b><center>Citations\n</center> </b></u>
    <ul>
<li>These are put at the end of the idea paraphrased\n</li>
<li>Direct quotes include author\'s’ name(s),publication year and page number(s).\n
e.g(Joseph,2007,p.35).\n</li>
<li>Make reference to author and year of publication if just paraphrasing.\n
e.g(Joseph,2007)\n</li>
    <li>If you have mentioned the author’s name only include year of publication.\n</li>
    </ul>
        <b>References to Authors\n\n</b>
        <ul>
    <li>When referring to two authors you can use:\n</li>
    <li>For example According to Sheldon and Amy(2018) or  (Sheldon and Amy,2018).\n</li>
    <li>When referring to three to five authors you can use.\n</li>
    <li>For example According to Walter,Howard and Leonard(2011) or\n
	(Walter,Howard,  and ,Leonard,2011).\n
(put comma before &amp; after  &amp;)\n</li>
    <li>When referring to six or more Authors use\n</li>

    <li>For example According to Amy et al(2016) or (James et al,2016).\n</li>
</ul>
    <u><b><center>References\n</center></b></u>
    <ul>
        <li>Should be labelled “References” and be in a new page.\n</li>
        <li>Should be arranged in the alphabetical order.\n</li>
    </ul>
        <u><b>Sample apa\n\n</b></u>
<li>https://owl.purdue.edu/owl/research_and_citation/apa_style/apa_formatting_and_style_guide/apa_sample_paper.html</li>




    </string>
    <string name="first_chicago">
        <u><b><center>CHICAGO\n</center></b></u>
       <B>First Page/header\n</B>
        <ul>
            <li>The title should be centered below the upper one third of the paper in CAPS.\n</li>

        </ul>

<b>Title Page\n</b>
<b>First Page\n</b>
        <ul>
            <li>Page numbers begin in the header of the first page of text aligned right.\n</li>
            <li>The text of the paper begins with a new line indented 0.5.\n</li>
            <li>This page has no title.\n</li>
        </ul>
        </string>
    <string name="last_chicago">
        <u>Citations\n</u>
        <ul>
<li>Place a superscript after a quote or paraphrase.\n</li>
<li>From the reference menu select insert footnote in MS word.\n</li>
<li>Insert a numeric endnote marker to let reader be  aware you are going to cite a source.\n</li>
<li>Indicate the source in an endnote at the end of your paper.\n</li>
<li>It should follow the format\n
{ Endnote number, Authors first and last name,Title of the resource in italics (City of Publication,publisher,Year of publication),Page Number }\n\n</li>
</ul>
<u>References\n\n</u>
        <li>The authors names are given as they appear on the publication you have used.\n</li>
<li>Use consistent capitalisation.\n</li>
        <li>Titles and subtitles of books are given maximal capitalisation.\n</li>
    <li>Capitalize Titles and subtitles of books.\n</li>
<li>All words other than prepositions, conjunctions and articles are capitalised\n.</li>
<li>Italicise book titles when typing or underlined when handwritten\n</li>.

        <u><b>Sample Chicago\n\n</b></u>
<li>https://owl.purdue.edu/owl/research_and_citation/chicago_manual_17th_edition/cmos_formatting_and_style_guide/cmos_nb_sample_paper.html</li>



    </string>
    <string name="first_mla">
    <u><b><center> MLA \n</center></b></u>
        <B><center>First page &amp; Header\n</center></B>
        <ul>
<li>On the top right corner write your last name .\n</li>
	<li>Using insert tab select Blank header then right align your name in MS word.\n</li>
<li>Then insert page number after last name\n</li>
	<li>In Insert tab select page number\n</li>
        </ul>
        <u>First page\n\n</u>
<ul>

    <li>On the first page write\n</li>
    <li><center>Your name\n</center></li>
    <li><center>Teacher/Professors name\n</center></li>
    <li><center>Course Name\n</center></li>
    <li><center>Date of submission\n</center></li>
    <li>Each on its line ,then align the information left.\n</li>
</ul>
        <u>Second Page.\n\n</u>

    <ul>
        <li>Write title of your essay in Title case.\n</li>
        <li>First paragraph is left aligned with the first sentence starting away from the margin.\n</li>
        <li>Use tab key to implement this.\n</li>
    </ul>
</string>
    <string name="last_mla">
       <u><B><center>Citations\n</center></B></u>
        <ul>
<li>In MLA  in-text citations contain information about  the author of the page number with no comma between them,they(citations)are put at the end of the idea paraphrased.\n</li>
<li>Example : (Charles 1991).\n\n</li>
<li>If the authors name is mentioned in text while paraphrasing the idea only the page number is included into parenthesis.\n</li>
<li>Citations are separated by a semicolon when citing multiple sources in the same reference parenthesis.\n</li>
            <li>Example (John 65;Smith 71).\n</li>
        </ul>

        <B><center><u>References to Author(s).\n\n</u></center></B>
        <ul>
            <li>When citing two authors use the format\n
            “    According to John and Smith,...(113)   ”  in the text of the paper or “ (John and Smith 113) “in the parenthesis.\n</li>
            <li>When citing three or more authors use the format\n</li>
            <li>“   According to John et al.,...(113)   “ in the text of the paper or (John et al.113)  “ in\n</li>
            <li>The parenthesis.\n\n</li>
        </ul>
        <B><center>Works Cited\n\n</center></B>
    <ul>

        <li>This section should appear at the end of the paper and begin on a new page separate from the other text.\n</li>
        <li>It should be labelled “Works Cited ” in Title case.\n</li>
        <li>Sources should be arranged in alphabetical order.\n</li>
</ul>
        <u><b>Sample MLA\n\n</b></u>
<li>https://owl.purdue.edu/owl/research_and_citation/mla_style/mla_formatting_and_style_guide/documents/20180702110400_747-2.pdf
</li>



    </string>
    <string name="first_harvard">
    <u><b><center>HARVARD\n</center> </b></u>
    <u><center>First Page &amp; Header\n</center></u>
    <B><center>Header\n</center></B>
            <ul>
<li>This part contains a short description of the title that should be present on each page and the page number. The information in the header is aligned right.\n</li>
<li>First Page\n</li>
<li><center>Halfway down the page is the title of the paper in CAPS.\n</center></li>
<li><center>Three lines down the title write the students name.\n</center></li>
<li><center>Four lines down write the name of the course.\n</center></li>
<li><center>Next  line is the name of professor/Teacher.\n</center></li>
<li><center>Next line is name of the institution(University).\n</center></li>
<li><center>Next line is name of state or city where the university is located.\n</center></li>
<li><center>Then date.\n</center></li>
        </ul>



    </string>
    <string name="last_harvard">
        <ul>
        <li>Title in the next page should start the page and should be centered,not in CAPS not bolded,not underlined
            or italicized and written in Title Case.\n</li>
</ul>
<u><center>Citation.\n\n</center></u>

            <ul>
<li>Authors last name and the year of publication for the source should be stated in the text.\n</li>
<li>Unlike APA there is no comma between authors name and the year of publication in the in-text citation  eg (Robert 2011).\n</li>
<li>In-text citations are put just after the author or the authors work is mentioned: \n</li>
<li>Example: ... a recent study (Cooper 2013) has described ....\n</li>

<li>If while paraphrasing the idea the author’s name is mentioned in the text, only the year of publication
            is included into parenthesis which directly follows. \n</li>
<li>Example: According to Smith (2009),\n</li>
            </ul>
            <ul>

        <u><center>Reference List \n\n</center></u>
        <li> The list of sources used in the paper should appear at the end of the paper. \n</li>
        <li> It should begin on a new page separate from the text of the essay. \n</li>
        <li> It may be labelled ‘References’ or ‘Reference List’.\n</li>

        <li> The words ‘References’ or ‘Reference List’ should be centered at the top of the page (NOT bolded, not underlined, not italicized, not in quotation marks).\n</li>
        <li> If you name the list of sources ‘Reference List’, please, mind that both words begin with a capital letter.\n</li>
        <li> All lines after the first line of each entry in the list should be indented one-half inch from the left margin to maintain the hanging indentation.\n</li>
        <li> Double-space all entries. \n</li>
        <li> Authors names are inverted (last name first). Do not put periods with the authors’ initials.\n</li>
        <li> The titles of books and periodicals are italicized in the Reference List as a rule. \n</li>
        <li> The articles or the chapters are not italicized. Use quotation marks for them. \n</li>
       <li> Sentence case is used for all the sources except the entire websites and journal titles.\n</li>


        </ul>
         <ul>

    </ul>


    </string>
    <string name="citation_process">

        <u><b>Citing  a source and Automatically formatting Bibliographies\n\n</b></u>
        <ul>
       <li>On the References tab,on Citations and Bibliography group,select the style you want to use for the citation.\n</li>
        <li>Click at the end of the sentence that you want to cite.\n</li>
       <li>Click Insert Citation and select Add New Source.\n</li>
        <li>In the Create Source box ,type in the citation details and then click OK.\n</li>
        <li>Next time you quote this reference just click Insert Citation and choose the citation you want to use.\n</li>
        <u>Create a Bibliography from your sources\n\n</u>
        <li>Click at the end of the document where you want to insert a bibliography.\n</li>
        <li>On the References tab in the citations &amp; Bibliography group,click Bibliogpaphy.\n</li>
        </ul>
                <u><b>Citation In Word\n\n</b></u>
<li>https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/office/create-a-bibliography-citations-and-references</li>
    </string>


</resources>
